fyvor.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy - Fyvor.com

#### Privacy Statement

Fyvor is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site Fyvor.

Please Contact Us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us via postal mail at the following address:

MK InfoTech Limited  
20F JinHui Tower  
No 8 WuZhong Rd, XuHui  
Shanghai, China 200336  
Telephone: +86-21-64188525  
Email:support@fyvor.com  
Director: Ran Chen  

#### Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, Fyvor collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from Fyvor, our servers log your IP address.

Fyvor only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

#### How We Collect or Create Information

Your activity on our site (such as pages viewed, searches performed and features accessed);   
Operating system, web browser information, and device attributes;   
Inbound-referral and outbound websites;   
Your internet protocol (“IP”) address;   
The dates and times that you visited or used our site, or requested certain services or transactions.

Cookies and Web Beacons: A cookie is a small text file or identifier. When you visit a Site, we may store one or more cookies or other similar information on your device.

#### How we Use Your Information

We may use information that we collect for the following purposes:

  * Operate, maintain, and improve our site and our other products and services;
  * Monitor and improve marketing and promotional campaigns and efforts;
  * Provide you with a personalized experience on and off our site, including targeted advertisements and promotions;
  * Anonymize and aggregate information for different purposes, such as website traffic flow analysis, usage analysis, product development, market analysis, case studies, reports, insights, and marketing;
  * Comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements; 
  * Share information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may combine information about you collected across different Services and devices, and we may combine information we obtain with information obtained from third parties. We may make inferences based on this combined information, such as product preferences and interests. We retain all information we collect about you for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### Intellectual Property Rights

Except for User Submissions, all of the content, arrangement and layout of the Sites and Services, including, but not limited to, any trademarks, service marks, text, images and other content or copyrightable material, and the compilation of the foregoing (collectively, the “Content”) are the sole and exclusive property of Fyvor. Any unauthorized use of the Content or Fyvor Marks is strictly prohibited and may violate civil or criminal laws, including, but not limited to, copyright laws, trademark laws, and the laws of privacy and publicity.

#### Third Party Cookies 

**Analytics** : We may allow third parties to use tracking devices through our products to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as Fyvor does for itself. For example, Fyvor has relationships with third party advertising technology and analytics companies, such as Google Analytics to perform tracking and reporting functions for our products.

**Affiliate Network** : Fyvor is in relation with Affiliate Networks, such as Commission Junction, LinkShare, ShareaSale, with whom we partner to provide certain offers, promotions or features available on or through our products and when you click on links provided by Affiliate Networks and buy something, we will earn a small commission from the advertiser at no additional cost to you. When you leave our site to a merchant's site through one of the affiliate networks coupons or offers, Affiliate Networks will use cookies, pixels or other similar technologies on our products to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, content viewed, search terms, location of the device, a cookie identifier, communication type (broadband or dial-up), and browser-related properties).

#### Your Choices 

Cookies and Pixel Tags. You may stop or restrict cookies and pixel tags on your computer or purge cookies from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. However, if you “turn off,” purge, or disable cookies or pixel tags, although you may still use our site, you may not be able to use all of the features, functions, or services available on our site.

Location Based Services. You may opt-out of having your Precise Location Data collected by Fyvor.com at any time by editing the appropriate setting on your mobile device (which is usually located in the Settings area of your device).

#### Children and Privacy

Fyvor encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

#### Individuals under 13

No information should be submitted on Fyvor by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. Fyvor does not provide any personally-identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

#### Links to Other Sites

Fyvor contains links to sites other than Fyvor; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Fyvor.

#### How this Privacy Policy May Change

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and all changes will be effective at the time we post them. If we believe there is a significant change to this Privacy Policy or our data collection and use practices, we will indicate on our websites that our Privacy Policy has changed prior to the change becoming effective. The then-posted version of the Privacy Policy supersedes all prior versions. Your continued access to or use of any of our site shall be deemed your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.
